Guide to the Watkins Loomis Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Uncataloged Contracts and Miscellaneous Documents
  - Cousins, Sheila (Ronald Matthews) (Box 145)
  - Cowles, Virginia Spencer (Box 145)
  - Coxe, Howard C. (Box 145)
  - Cram, Mildred (Box 145)
  - Crosby, Emma Yvonne "Everett Young" (Box 145)
  - Crownfield, Gertrude (Box 145)
  - Crowther, J.G. (Box 145)
  - Croy, Homer (Box 145)
  - Dakers, Andrew (Box 145)
  - Davenport, Marcia (Box 145)
  - Davenport, Russell (Box 145)
  - Davis, Forrest (Box 145)
  - Davis, George (Box 145)
  - Davis, Hartley (Box 145)
  - Dearden, Harold (Box 145)
  - Dearden, Seton (Box 145)
  - Decker, Phelps (Box 145)
  - Deeping, Warwick (Box 145)
  - DeGrouchy, William J. (Box 145)
  - Deitrick, Janet (Box 145)
  - Delafield, Clelia Benjamin & Dorothy Hamilton Dick (Box 145)
  - De Vautibault, Elizabeth Gilbert (Box 145)
  - Del Vayo, Julio Alvarez (Box 145)
  - Dewing, E.B. (Box 145)
  - Dillon, Jean or Sean (Box 146)
  - Disque, Brice, Jr. (Box 146)
  - Divine, Arthur D. (Box 146)
  - Dixon, Peter (Box 146)
  - Dobson, Ruth Lininger (Box 146)
  - Donahoe, Edward (Box 146)
  - Donovan, Frances R. (Box 146)
  - Douglas, Eileen (Box 146)
  - Doyle, William R. (Box 146)
  - Dryden, Elizabeth (Box 146)
  - Du Bois, William (Box 146)
  - Duff, Charles (Box 146)
  - Duggan, Pat (T. Walter Duggan) (Box 146)
  - Dunham, Curtis (Box 146)
  - Dunn, Robert (Box 146)
  - Eaton, Evelyn (Box 146)
  - Ebenhack, Arthur (Box 146)
  - Edgar, Day (Box 146)
  - Eichler, Lillian (Box 146)
  - Ekman, Karl (Box 146)
  - Elliot, Geraldine (Box 146)
  - Emerson, Jerry (Box 146)
  - Emmons, K.B. & George Randolph Chester (Box 146)
  - Endore, Guy (Box 146)
  - Engstrand, Stuart David (Box 146)
  - Fairway, Sidney (Box 146)
  - Farjeon, Eleanor (Box 146)
  - Ferris, Walter (Box 146)
  - Fessier, Michael (Box 146)
  - French, Yvonne (Box 146)
  - Field, Virginia (Margaret St. John Field) (Box 146)
  - Filchner, Wilhelm (Box 146)
  - Finn, Rex Welldon (Box 146)
  - Fishbein, Frieda (Box 146)
  - Fisher, Dorothy Canfield (Box 146)
  - Fisher, John (Box 146)
  - Fitzgerald, Sheila & Maeve O'Callaghan (Box 146)
  - Fitzgerald, William F. (Box 146)
  - Flaccus, Kimball (Box 146)
  - Flebbe, Beulah Marie Dix (Box 146)
  - Fletcher, Dorothy (Box 146)
  - Flynn, Brian (Box 146)
  - Foley, Martha (Mrs Whit Burnett) (Box 147)
  - Forbes, Joan Rosita Torr (Box 147)
  - Forgione, Luigi (Box 147)
  - Forrest, Belford (Box 147)
  - Foster, Michael (Box 147)
  - Fox, Ralph (Box 147)
  - Frank, Gerold (Box 147)
  - Franken, Rose (Box 147)
  - Freeman, Helen (Box 147)
  - Frost, Elizabeth Hollister (Box 147)
  - Fuller, John Frederick Charles (Box 147)
  - Fuller, Sarita (Box 147)
  - Garvin, Marie Ballou (Box 147)
  - Gibbon, Perceval (Box 147)
  - Gibbons, Stella (Stella Webb) (Box 147)
  - Gilbert, Morris (Box 147)
  - Gilder, Rodman (Box 147)
  - Gizycka, Countess Felicia (Mrs Drew Pearson) (Box 147)
  - Glaspell, Susan (Box 147)
  - Gorer, Geoffrey (Box 147)
  - Gorman, Herbert (Box 147)
  - Goudge, Elizabeth de Beauchamp (Box 147)
  - Green, Frederick Lawrence (Box 147)
  - Greene, Ward (Box 147)
  - Greyson, Joan - agent (Box 147)
  - Gribble, Harry Wagstaff & Edwin Greenwood (Box 147)
  - Gropper, Milton Herbert (Box 147)
  - Gross, Milt (Box 147)
  - Gubsky, Micholai (Box 147)
  - Gumpert, Martin (Box 147)
  - Guthrie, Ramon (Box 147)
  - Hackney, Louise Wallace (Box 147)
  - Haggard, Stephen Hubert Avenal (Box 147)
  - Hallet, Richard Matthews (Box 147)
  - Hansl, Jean Archibald (Box 147)
  - Hardy, Jocelyn Lee (Box 147)
  - Hardy, W. George (Box 147)
  - Harman, Neal (Box 147)
  - Harman, Hugh & Rudolf C. Ising (Box 147)
  - Harrison, George Bagshawe (Box 147)
  - Haslip, Joan (Box 147)
  - Hatch, Alden (Box 147)
  - Hatch, Eric Stow (Box 147)
  - Hatch, Sylvia S. (Box 147)
  - Hauser, Odell & Elmer Davis (Box 147)
  - Haviland-Taylor, Katharine (Box 147)
  - Hawthorne, Hazel (Box 147)
  - Heard, Gerald & Aldous Huxley (Box 148)
  - Hersch, Virginia (Box 148)
  - Henri, Ernst (Box 148)
  - Herbert, Elizabeth Hamilton (Box 148)
  - Hershey, Burnet (Box 148)
  - Hibben, Paxton Pattison (Box 148)
  - Hibbert, Eloise Talcott (Box 148)
  - Hill, Fowler (Box 148)
  - Hitchcock, Mary (Box 148)
  - Hoffman, Richard H. (Box 148)
  - Hohman, Leslie B. (Box 148)
  - Holmes, F. Ratcliffe (Box 148)
  - Holstius, E. Nils (Box 148)
  - Holt, Henry (Box 148)
  - Horler, Sydney (Box 148)
  - Hosken, Clifford (Box 148)
  - Howard, Sidney & Carl Van Doren (Box 148)
  - Hunt, Bob (Box 148)
  - Hume, Cyril (Box 148)
  - Hurn, Philip (Box 148)
  - Hurston, Zora Neale (Box 148)
  - Hyde, Robert & John Mersereau (Box 148)
  - Ilma, Viola (Box 148)
  - Ingham, Travis (Box 148)
  - Irby, Christian (Box 148)
  - Jacobs, Helen Hull (Box 148)
  - Jameson, Storm (Margaret Storm Jameson) (Box 148)
  - Jenks, Almet & Adelyn Bushnell (Box 148)
  - Jellinek, Oskar (Box 148)
  - Johann, Zita (Box 148)
  - Jones, Elizabeth Inglis (Box 148)
  - Jones, F. Elwyn (Box 148)
  - Jordan, Elizabeth (Box 148)
  - Josephy, Helen & Mary Margaret McBride (Box 148)
  - Joslyn, Peggy (Box 148)
  - Kafka, Roger & Ira Slomon, Jr. "Ira Bentley" (Box 148)
  - Kahler, Wood (Box 148)
  - Karlton, Kelm (Box 148)
  - Keating, Micheline (Box 148)
  - Keating, Pearl (Box 148)
  - Keelock, Harold (Box 148)
  - Kennedy, Harold J. (Box 148)
  - Kenyon, Bernice (Box 148)
  - King, Beulah (Box 148)
  - Kingsmill, Hugh (Box 148)
  - Kinross, Albert (Box 148)
  - Kline, Virginia (Box 148)
  - Knight, Clifford (Box 148)
  - Kolodin, Irving (Box 148)
  - Kuhn, Irene (Box 148)
  - Kummer, Frederic Arnold "Arnold Fredericks" (Box 148)
  - Kutner, Nanette (Box 148)
  - Lackey, Jean & Margarita Moreno Cockran (Box 148)
  - Laing, Alexander Kinnan (Box 148)
  - Landau, Rom (Box 148)
  - Lane, Margaret (Mrs Bryan Wallace) (Box 148)
  - Langdon-Davies, John (Box 148)
  - Langsner, Clara (Box 148)
  - Lascelles, Ernita (Box 148)
  - Laver, James (Box 148)
  - Lawrence, David Herbert (Box 148)
  - Lee, Auriol (Box 148)
  - Leighton, Isabel & Gene Cohn (Box 148)
  - Lenihan, Winifred (Box 148)
  - Leonard, Martin (Box 148)
  - Levin, Meyer (Box 148)
  - Levy, Robert (Box 148)
  - Lewis, Lorna (Box 148)
  - Lewis, Sinclair (Box 149)
  - Lewis, Sinclair (photocopies) (Box 149A)
  - Liddell-Hart, Sir Basil Henry (Box 150)
  - Liepmann, Heinz (Box 150)
  - Littell, Robert (Box 150)
  - Lowenstein-Wertheim-Freudenberg, Hubertus, Prinz zu (Box 150)
  - Long, John Cuthbert (Box 150)
  - Long, Renee (Box 150)
  - Longmans Green & Co., Ltd. (Box 150)
  - Low, Gardner (Charles Rhodda) (Box 150)
  - MacArthur, D. Wilson "David Wilson"• (Box 150)
  - McCall, Monica - agent (Box 150)
  - McCarthy, John (Box 150)
  - McCoy, Horace (Box 150)
  - McDermott, John (Box 150)
  - MacDonald, Laetitia Irwin (Box 150)
  - Macdougall, Allan Ross (Box 150)
  - McGinnis, Allen (Box 150)
  - McGuire, Karl (Box 150)
  - McLaughlin, Alice Krug & Virginia Swain (Box 150)
  - Manning, Bruce (Box 150)
  - Manning-Sanders, Ruth (Box 150)
  - March, Joe (Box 150)
  - Marjoribanks, Edward (Box 150)
  - Markham, Virgil (Box 150)
  - Marks, Maurice & Fred Thompson (Box 150)
  - Marlowe, Dave (Box 150)
  - Marshall, Bruce (Box 150)
  - Marston, Jeffrey (Box 150)
  - Mason, Charles Haynes (Box 150)
  - Matson, Norman & Joseph Schrank (Box 150)
  - Matson & Duggan - agents (Harold Matson & Pat Duggan) (Box 150)
  - Matthews, Arthur Guy & Theodore Jaeckel (Box 150)
  - Matthews, Herbert L. (Box 150)
  - Mauck, Hilda (Hilda Mauck Holmes) (Box 150)
  - Merritt, Abraham (Box 150)
  - Mersereau, John (Box 150)
  - Messner, Kathryn G. (Box 150)
  - Miele, Elizabeth (Box 150)
  - Miller, Max (Box 150)
  - Mitchell, Ruth Comfort (Box 150)
  - Moffitt, John C. (Box 150)
  - Monahan, James (Box 150)
  - Moore, Austin (Box 150)
  - Moray, Alexander (Box 150)
  - Moorhead, Ethel (Box 150)
  - Morgan, Ainsworth (Box 151)
  - Morgan, Deck (?) - Morgan Deck (Box 151)
  - Morrison, Lee (Box 151)
  - Morton, J.B. "Beachcomber" (Box 151)
  - Moss, Frank L. (Box 151)
  - Muggeridge, Malcolm (Box 151)
  - Muir, Charles Augustus (Box 151)
  - Murray, Sinclair (Box 151)
  - Myers, Henry (Box 151)
  - Newton, Douglas (Box 151)
  - Niles, Blair (Box 151)
  - Nizovoy, Pavel (Box 151)
  - Norwood, Hayden (Box 151)
  - O'Brien, Edward Joseph Harrington (Box 151)
  - O'Brien, Kate (Box 151)
  - O'Dell, Scott (Box 151)
  - Oliver, George W. (George W. Howe & Oliver Eastwood) (Box 151)
  - Oliver, Shirling (Box 151)
  - O'Mallory, Ida Beatrice (Box 151)
  - Ornitz, Sadie L. & Vera Caspary (Box 151)
  - Ornitz, Samuel (Box 151)
  - O'Shaughnessy, Edith Coues (Box 151)
  - Parker, Robert Allerton (Box 151)
  - Parrott, Ursula (Box 151)
  - Parsons, Alice Beal (Box 151)
  - Pascal, Ernest (Box 151)
  - Patrick, Diana (Desemea Wilson) (Box 151)
  - Pearn, Pollinger & Higham Ltd. - agents (Box 151)
  - Pearson, Hesketh (Box 151)
  - Peckham, Ted (Box 151)
  - Pedersen, Victor Cox (Box 151)
  - Pelletier, Louis, Jr. (Box 151)
  - Pember, Evelyn T (Box 151)
  - A.D. Peters, Literary Agent (Box 151)
  - Peterson, Margaret (Box 151)
  - Pezet, Alfonso Washington (Box 151)
  - Philby, Harry St.John Bridger (Box 151)
  - Pierce, Evelyn Miller (Box 151)
  - Pinchot, Ann (Box 151)
  - Porter, Sara Coleman (Box 151)
  - Porterfield, Anita "Anne Burr" (Box 151)
  - Pound, Arthur & Samuel Taylor Moore (Box 151)
  - Powell, Dawn (Box 152)
  - Powell, Lyman Pierson (Box 152)
  - Powell, Talcott Williams (Box 152)
  - Praytor, Al & Tom Lewis (Box 152)
  - Press and Publisher Literary Service (Moscow) (Box 152)
  - Pribichevich, Stoyan (Box 152)
  - Priestley, John Boynton & Gerald Bullett (Box 152)
  - Pryce-Jones, Alan Payan (Box 152)
  - Pym, Micheal (Box 152)
  - Ralston, Marjorie (Box 152)
  - Rand, Ayn (Box 152)
  - Rapp, William Jourdan (Box 152)
  - Reed, Daniel (Box 152)
  - Reiley, Franklin Claxton (Box 152)
  - Reyher, Ferdinand (Box 152)
  - Reynolds, Minnie (Box 152)
  - Rice, Craig (Box 152)
  - Richardson, Anthony (Box 152)
  - Rideout, Ransom (Box 152)
  - Rinehart, Mary Roberts (Box 152)
  - Rising, Lawrence (Box 152)
  - Rives, Amelie (Princess Pierre Troubetzkoy) (Box 152)
  - Roberts, Carl Eric Bechhofer (Box 153)
  - Roberts, Harry (Box 153)
  - Robertson, C.P.N. (Box 153)
  - Robinson, W.W. & Irene B. (Box 153)
  - Rodocanachi, C.P. (Box 153)
  - Rostron, Sir Arthur (Box 153)
  - Roughead, William (Box 153)
  - Rowse, Alfred Leslie (Box 153)
  - Royle, Edwin Milton (Box 153)
  - Royden, Agnes Maude (Box 153)
  - Rubenstein, Marion (Box 153)
  - St. Joseph, Ellis (Box 153)
  - Salkow, Sidney (Box 153)
  - Salt, Sarah (Box 153)
  - Sampson, Richard Hull "Richard Hull" (Box 153)
  - Samuels, Lesser (Box 153)
  - Sapieha, Princess Paul (Box 153)
  - Saslavski, Luis (Box 153)
  - Savage, Valerie (Box 153)
  - Saxby, Charles & Louis Molnar (Box 153)
  - Sayers, Dorothy Leigh (Box 153)
  - Schrank, Joseph, Norman Matson, & Philip Dunning (Box 153)
  - Scott, Reginald T. Maitland (Box 153)
  - Scot-Watson, K. (Box 153)
  - Seabrook, Katie (Box 153)
  - Seabrook, William Buehler (Box 153)
  - Seelig, Florence Rayner (Box 153)
  - Selmark, George (Leslie Seldon Truss) (Box 153)
  - Shackleton, Edward (Box 154)
  - Shaw, Irwin (Box 154)
  - Sheean, Vincent (Box 154)
  - Sheepshanks, Beatrice (Box 154)
  - Sheppard, Hugh Richard Lawrie (Box 154)
  - Shipman, Nell (Box 154)
  - Shkvarkin, V.V. (Box 154)
  - Silvercruys, Suzanne (Box 154)
  - Sitwell, Sir Osbert (Box 154)
  - Skinner, Dickson (Box 154)
  - Slocombe, George (Box 154)
  - Smith, Gordon Arthur (Box 154)
  - Smith, Margaret Lyon (Box 154)
  - Smith, Thorne (Box 154)
  - Snowden, Nicholas (Box 154)
  - Sofaer, Abraham (Box 154)
  - Solomon, Gwladys Cowper Smith (Box 154)
  - Sparkes, Boyden (Box 154)
  - Sparks, Ethel "Beldon Duff" (Box 154)
  - Speaight, Robert (Box 154)
  - Speare, Dorothy (Box 154)
  - Sprigg, C. St.John (Box 154)
  - Spring, Howard (Box 154)
  - Stark, Mabel (Box 155)
  - Starling, Lyn (Box 155)
  - Steele, Wilbur Daniel (Box 155)
  - Stevenson, Sylvia (Box 155)
  - Stiles, Pauline (Box 155)
  - Stoddard, Lothrop (Box 155)
  - Stokes, Leslie & Sewell (Box 155)
  - Stone, Austin (Box 155)
  - Stong, Phil & Virginia Swain Stong (Box 155)
  - Storm, Dinah (Box 155)
  - Story magazine (Box 155)
  - Strabel, Thelma (Box 155)
  - Strindberg, Frida Uhl (Mrs August) (Box 155)
  - Strong, Patience (Box 155)
  - Strunk, Roland (Box 155)
  - Sturm, Justin (Box 155)
  - Sullivan, Alan (Box 155)
  - Swerling, Jo & James Whittaker "Tiffany Wells" (Box 155)
  - Symon, Bert (Box 155)
  - Taylor, Gay (Box 156)
  - Taylor, F. Sherwood (Box 156)
  - Taylor, Leila (Box 156)
  - Taylor, Ross McLaury (Box 156)
  - Teague, Walter Dorwin (Box 156)
  - Thane, Elswyth (Box 156)
  - Thayer, Francis (Box 156)
  - Thayer, Mary Van Rensselaer & Huilan Koo (Box 156)
  - Thielen, Benedict (Box 156)
  - Thomas, Aeronwy (Box 156)
  - Thomas, Alan Ernest Wentworth (Box 156)
  - Thomas, Dolores (Box 156)
  - Thompson, Valentine (Box 156)
  - Thorne, Anthony (Box 156)
  - Tilsley, Frank (Box 156)
  - Tobenkin, Elias (Box 156)
  - Totheroh, Dan (Box 156)
  - Trench, P.S. LeP. & John Brooks (Box 156)
  - Tuckerman, Arthur (Box 156)
  - Turner, John V. "Nicholas Brady" & "David Hume" (Box 156)
  - Turney, Robert (Box 156)
  - Ullman, Alice Woods (Box 156)
  - Vaughn, Miles W. (Box 156)
  - Vernon, Frank & Virginia (Box 156)
  - Von Behr, H.A. (Box 156)
  - Von Tempski, Armine (Box 156)
  - Von Ulm, Gerith (Box 156)
  - Vorse, Mary Heaton (Box 156)
  - Vosper, Frank (Box 156)
  - Waite, Phyllis (Box 156)
  - Wakefield, H. Russell (Box 156)
  - Wallace, Doreen (Box 156)
  - Walters, William J. (Box 156)
  - Warshawsky, Samuel J. (Box 156)
  - Warwick, James (Box 156)
  - Washburn, Robert Collyer & Helen (Box 156)
  - Watson, Elliot Lovegood Grant (Box 156)
  - Watson, Francis (Box 156)
  - Waugh, Arthur (Box 156)
  - Wavell, Archibald Percival Wavell, 1st Earl (Box 156)
  - Webster, Ben (Box 156)
  - Weiman, Rita (Box 156)
  - Weiss, Edward (Box 156)
  - Welch, Patrick (Box 156)
  - Wells, Linton (Box 156)
  - Webb, Jon Edgar (Box 156)
  - West, Geoffrey (Box 156)
  - Weston, Herbert & John Ballantine Porter (Box 156)
  - Wetmore, Elizabeth (Box 156)
  - Wharton, Edith Newbold Jones (Box 157-159)
  - Whipple, Dorothy (Box 159A)
  - Whipple, Sidney B. (Box 159A)
  - Whistler, Laurence (Box 159A)
  - White, Ethel Lina (Box 159A)
  - White, Nelia Gardner (Box 159A)
  - White, Terence Hanbury (Box 159A)
  - Whitney, Janet Payne (Box 159A)
  - Whiton, Augustus Sherrill (Box 159A)
  - Whiton, Louis C. & Corinne Harris Markey (Box 159A)
  - Wickware, Francis Sill (Box 159A)
  - Wiley, John (Box 159A)
  - Will, Harold (Box 159A)
  - Willert, Sir Arthur (Box 159A)
  - Willetts, Eliza (Box 159A)
  - Williams, Charles (Box 159A)
  - Wilson, Margaret (Box 159A)
  - Wilson, R. McNair "Anthony Wynne" (Box 159A)
  - Winwar, Frances (Francesca Viciguerra Grebanier) (Box 159A)
  - Wolff, William Almon, Achmed Abdullah, et al. (Box 159A)
  - Woods, Alice (Box 159A)
  - Woodward, W.E. (Box 159A)
  - Worthington, Marjorie (Box 159A)
  - Wren, Percival Christopher (Box 159A)
  - Yeats-Brown, Francis Charles Claypon (Box 159A)
  - Young, Francis Brett (Box 159A)
  - Yousoupoff, Felix Felixovitch, Prince (Box 159A)
- Series VI: Financial
  Account books; ledgers, cash disbursements, cash receipts; payroll; journal; trial balances; commissions; petty cash, etc.
  - Authors, 1928-1936 (Box 160)
  - Publishers, 1932-1934 (Box 160)
  - Ledger, 1927-1930 (Box 161)
  - Ledger, 1927-1930 (Box 161)
  - Ledger, 1929-1930 (Box Flatbox 350)
  - Cash Disbursements, 1930-1933 (Box Flatbox 350)
  - Cash Receipts, 1930-1934 (Box Flatbox 351)
  - Ledger, 1931-1936 (Box 161)
  - General ledger, 1931-1934 (Box 162)
  - Payroll book, 1931-1951 (Box 162)
  - Cash disbursments, 1933-1935 (Box Flatbox 351)
  - Cash receipts, 1934-1937 (Box Flatbox 351)
  - Cash disbursments, 1935-1937 (Box Flatbox 352)
  - Journal & ledger, 1935-1937 (Box 162)
  - Cash disbursments, 1937-1939 (Box Flatbox 352)
  - Cash receipts, 1937-1939 (Box Flatbox 352)
  - Ledger, 1938-1947 (Box 162)
  - Ledger, 1938-1952 (Box 163)
  - Ledger, 1938-1953 (Box 163)
  - Cash disbursments, 1939-1940 (Box Flatbox 353)
  - Cash receipts, 1939-1941 (Box Flatbox 353)
  - Cash receipts, 1940-1942 (Box 163)
  - Trial balance, 1940-1942 (Box 163)
  - Trial balance, 1941 (Box 163)
  - Trial balance, 1941-1942 (Box Flatbox 353)
  - Trial balance, 1941-1953 (Box 164)
  - Cash receipts, 1941-1943 (Box Flatbox 354)
  - Commissions, 1941-1942 (Box 164)
  - Ledger, 1942-1947 (Box 164)
  - Cash disbursments, 1942-1944 (Box Flatbox 354)
  - Cash Receipts, 1943-1945 (Box Flatbox 354)
  - Commissions, 1943 (Box 165)
  - Commissions, 1944 (Box 165)
  - Commissions, 1944-1946 (Box Flatbox 354)
  - Commissions, 1945 (Box 165)
  - Trial balance, 1945 (Box 165)
  - Trial balance, 1945-1947 (Box Flatbox 355)
  - Trial balance, 1946 (Box 165)
  - Trial balance, 1946 (Box 165)
  - Cash disbursments, 1946-1947 (Box Flatbox 355)
  - Cash disbursments, 1947 (Box 165)
  - Trial balance, 1947 (Box 165)
  - Trial balance, 1947-1949 (Box Flatbox 355)
  - Ledger, 1948 (Box 165)
  - Trail balance, 1948 (Box 165)
  - Trail balance, 1949 (Box 165)
  - Cash disbursments, 1949-1951 (Box Flatbox 356)
  - 1950 (Box 166)
  - Cash receipts, 1950-1952 (Box Flatbox 356)
  - 1950-1953 (Box 166)
  - Cash disbursments, 1951-1952 (Box Flatbox 356)
  - 1952-1953 (Box 166)
  - 1953-1954 (Box 166)
  - General ledger, 1953-1965 (Box 166)
  - 1954-1973 (Box 166)
  - Cash payamnts, 1953-1957 (Box Flatbox 357)
  - Monthly balance, 1954-1960 (Box 167)
  - 1955-1956 (Box 167)
  - 1956-1958 (Box 167)
  - 1958-1959 (Box 167)
  - 1960-1961 (Box 167)
  - 1961-1963 (Box 167)
  - Trial balance, 1961-1972 (Box 168)
  - 1963-1964 (Box 168)
  - 1964-1965 (Box 168)
  - 1966-1967 (Box 168)
  - General ledgers & payroll ledgers, 1966-1975 (Box 169)
  - 1967-1968 (Box 169)
  - 1969-1970 (Box 169)
  - 1971-1972 (Box 169)
  - Annual reports, 1928-1948 (Box 170)
  - Cancelled checks to authors, 1957-1976 (Box 171)
  - Check stubs, 1968-1974 (Box 172)
  - Check stubs, 1974-1981 (Box 173)
  - Macy Newspaper Syndicate, Inc. (Box 173)
  - Account books, 1947-1952 (Box 180)
  - Account books, 1950-1957 (Box 181)
  - Account books, 1954-1960 (Box 182)
  - Account books, 1959-1965 (Box 183)
  - Account books, 1964-1971 (Box 184)
  - Submissions (Box 185)
- Series VII: Old Royalty Statements
  - Asquith, Lady Cynthia -- Adler, Polly -- Ba -- Badel, A. -- Be -- Bellaman -- Bi-Bu -- Bottome, Phyllis -- Boyle, Kay -- Bretherton, Vivian -- Burlingame, Roger -- Burnett, Francis Eliza Hodgson (Box 174)
  - Ca-Cl -- Carpenter, Margaret -- Carr, John Dixon -- Chase, Stuart -- Co-Cu -- Cole, G.D.H. & Margaret -- D -- David Hassoldt -- Davis, Thomas R.A. & Lydia -- Deeping, Warwick -- DeVries, Peter -- Diving, A. David (Box 175)
  - E -- Eaton, Evelyn -- Farjeon, Eleanor -- Fe-Fo -- Fr-Fu -- G -- Goudge, Elizabeth -- Gray, Madeling -- Ha-He -- Hatch, Alden -- Hathaway, Katherine Butler -- Hi-Hu -- J -- Jefferis, Barbara -- Jerrold, Douglas (Box 176)
  - K -- La-Le -- Laing, Alexander -- Lawrence, Hilda -- Li-Ly -- M -- Mc -- Marshall, Bruce -- Mauldin, William -- Moorehead, Alan -- Morris, Edita -- N -- O (Box 177)
  - P -- Poncius, Gontran Jean Pierre de Montaigne, Viconte de -- R -- Rand, Ayn -- Ray, Marie Benyon -- Rice, Craig -- Sa-Sn -- Salvemini, Gaetano -- Sayers, Dorothy leigh -- Seabrook, William Buelher -- Saeger, Allan -- Sitwell family -- Smith, Thorne (Box 178)
  - So-Sw -- Spring, Howard -- Strabel, Thelma -- Strong, Phil -- T -- Teague, Walter Darwin -- Thomas, Dylan -- V -- Wa-We -- Wagner, Geoffrey -- Wallace, Kathleen -- Wh -- Wi-Wy -- Williams, Charles -- Y (Box 179)
  - Taylor, Theodore Record album (Box 180)
- Series VIII: Card Files
  - Business cards, information cards on authors, "contracted books not yet delivered", (1 metal card file box) (Box 186)
  - "New York Solicitations & LHJ, McCalls", (1 card file box) (Box 186)
  - Manuscript submissions, A-O, (1 metal card file box) (Box 187)
  - Sold manuscripts, A-D (Box 188)
  - Sold manuscripts, E-O (Box 189)
  - Sold manuscripts, P-Z (Box 190)
  - Manuscript submissions, ABB-BLO (Box 191)
  - Manuscript submissions, BLU-CHU (Box 192)
  - Manuscript submissions, CIC-DON (Box 193)
  - Manuscript submissions, DOO-GOR (Box 194)
  - Manuscript submissions, GOS-IWA (Box 195)
  - Manuscript submissions, JAC-LEV (Box 196)
  - Manuscript submissions, LEW-MON (Box 197)
  - Manuscript submissions, MOO-QUI (Box 198)
  - Manuscript submissions, RAE-SKI (Box 199)
  - Manuscript submissions, SKO-URO (Box 200)
  - Manuscript submissions, VAE-WIS (Box 201)
  - Manuscript submissions, WIT-ZUR (Box 202)
  - Manuscript submissions, A-Z (Box 203)
  - Old contracts, A-Z (Box 204)
  - Copyright, A-Z (Box 205)
  - Theatre biography clippings, A-L (Box 206)
  - Theatre biography clippings, Mc-Z (Box 207)
- Series IX: Arranged Correspondence
  The firm changed its name from A. Watkins to Watkins Loomis In 1980. We have, therefore, reflected this change in our finding aids and RLIN records; however, most of the boxes In the collection retain the name A. Watkins on their lables
  - A miscellaneous
  - Adams, W. Howard (Box 1)
  - Albert, Gail (Box 1)
  - Alger, John (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Ernie (Box 1)
  - Arking, Linda (Box 2)
  - Armstrong, Chris (Box 2)
  - Arndt, Tina (Box 2)
  - Arnot, Michelle (Box 2)
  - Arnson, Cindy (Box 2)
  - Asher, Marty (Box 2)
  - Austin, Audrey (Box 2)
  - Avirgan, Tony & Martha Honey (Box 2)
  - B miscellaneous (Box 3)
  - Baird, Rod (Box 4)
  - Balaban, John (Box 4)
  - Bartlett, Kim (Box 4)
  - Basso, Hamilton (Box 4)
  - Baumbach, Jonathan (Box 4)
  - Bellamann, Henry (Box 4)
  - Benard, Robert (Box 4)
  - Bent, Bob (Box 4)
  - Bergner, Dan (Box 4)
  - Bierman, John (Box 5)
  - Bintliff, Russell (Box 5)
  - Blair, Gwenda (Box 6)
  - Block, Allen (Box 6)
  - Bobrow, Mark (Box 6)
  - Bonner, Ray (Box 6)
  - Book order file (Box 6)
  - Bosse, Malcolm (Box 6)
  - Bosworth, James Allan (Box 6)
  - Boucher, Joelle (Box 6)
  - Boyle, Kay (Box 7)
  - Brickhill, Paul (Box 8)
  - Broner, Esther (Box 8)
  - Brownlow, Kevin (Box 8)
  - Bunker, Edward (Box 9)
  - Burlingame, Roger (Box 9)
  - Burnett, Frances Hogdson (Box 10)
  - C miscellaneous (Box 10)
  - Carlisle, Olga (Box 11)
  - Chapman, Leigh (Box 12)
  - Chappell, Helen (Box 12)
  - Chesler, Phyllis (Box 12)
  - Churcher, Sharon (Box 12)
  - Cohen, Leonard (Box 12)
  - Cohen, Robert (Box 12)
  - Conrad, Peter (Box 12)
  - Cooper, Rand (Box 12)
  - Cooper, Rand (cont.) (Box 13)
  - Copyright deposit (Box 13)
  - Copyright law info (Box 13)
  - Costigan, Madeleine (Box 13)
  - Currie, Ellen (Box 13)
  - D miscellaneous (Box 14)
  - Dahl, Roald (Box 14)
  - Dahstrom, Sture (Box 15)
  - Dale, Alzina Stone (Box 15)
  - Dauer, Rosamond (Box 15)
  - Desanti, Dominique (Box 15)
  - DeVries, Peter (Box 15)
  - De Vries/Epstein (Box 16)
  - Djindjihashvili, Nodar (Box 16)
  - Dostal, Sudy (Box 16)
  - DuBois, William Pene (Box 16)
  - Dunleavy, Steve (Box 17)
  - Dunleavy, Yvonne (Box 17)
  - E miscellaneous (Box 17)
  - Edelman, Elaine (Box 17)
  - Eisler, Benita (Box 17)
  - Elkins, Michael (Box 17)
  - F miscellaneous (Box 18)
  - Faust, Irvin (Box 18)
  - Feingold, Ben (Box 18)
  - Fish, Nancy (Box 18)
  - Fleming, H.K. (Box 18)
  - Foundations (Box 18)
  - Frank, Micheal (Box 18)
  - Fussell, Betty (Box 19)
  - G miscellaneous (Box 20)
  - Gallo, Guy (Box 20)
  - Gam. Rita (Box 20)
  - Garis, Leslie (Box 20)
  - Gidding, Josh (Box 20)
  - Gilot, Francoise (Box 21)
  - Glazer, Myra (Box 21)
  - Glazier, Stephen (Box 22)
  - Gleason, Judith (Box 22)
  - Gleason, Judith (1980-) (Box 23)
  - Gotlieb, Sondra (Box 23)
  - Guest, Iain (Box 23)